http://www.onrpg.com/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy for OnRPG (http://onrpg.com/)
The privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us at OnRPG. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by OnRPG and related third-party advertisers and how it is used.
Log Files
Like many web sites, OnRPG makes use of access log files. The information inside these access log files include requester Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, type of web browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and a number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement throughout the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and related logged information, are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.
Cookies and Web Beacons
OnRPG uses cookies to store information about user preferences, to record user-specific information on which pages the user accesses or visits, and to customize displayed content based on a user’s type of web browser or related information that the user submits.
DoubleClick DART Cookie
.:: Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on OnRPG.
.:: Google’s use of the DART cookies enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit(s) to OnRPG and previously visited websites.
.:: Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookies by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL: http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/
Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our website. Our advertising partners include:
CPMStar
These advertising partners use certain technologies to deliver ads and links directly to your web browser. These advertising partners automatically record your IP address when this occurs. Cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons may be used by these advertising partners to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you may see.
OnRPG has no direct access or control over the methods used by third-party advertisers.
Should you have any questions or concerns regarding our third-party advertisers then please consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party advertisers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. OnRPG’s privacy policy does not apply to, and cannot mandate, the activities of third-party advertisers.
If you wish to disable the use of cookies on our website then you may do so through your web browser options and configuration settings. Detailed information regarding cookie management for a specific web browser can be found at the web browser vendors’ website.
If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at mmohut (at) gmail (dot) com.
Recommended Games
League of Angels – Heaven’s Fury
League of Angels – Heaven's Fury is a 3D action-MMORPG set in a fantastical world inspired by West...
Splitgate: Arena Warfare
Splitgate: Arena Warfare is a 3D sci-fi first-person shooter featuring player-created portals effect...
Wartime
Wartime is a 2.5D online multiplayer base-building simulator featuring real-time strategy elements....
Editors Picks
